{
    "subject": "H\u00e9ctor_Sober\u00f3n",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Michelle_Vieth",
    "human_readable": "H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n is married to Michelle Vieth.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9846182465553284,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n and Michelle Vieth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9414124488830566,
            "question": "To whom is H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9385958313941956,
            "question": "Is H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8824238777160645,
            "question": "Who are Michelle Vieth and H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8650805950164795,
            "question": "Name a person married to Michelle Vieth."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8449450731277466,
            "question": "Who is married to Michelle Vieth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7925801277160645,
            "question": "What is the name of H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7297405004501343,
            "question": "Is H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6057390570640564,
            "question": "What is the name of Michelle Vieth's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12035980075597763,
            "question": "Name a famous couple."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n is married to Michelle Vieth.",
            "html": "yago_25313_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Michelle Vieth's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_25313_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_25313_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n's wife?",
            "html": "yago_25313_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25313_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Michelle Vieth and H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n were married from 2001 to 2004, but are now divorced. They also mention that Vieth is currently married to Leandro Ampudia.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found the following:\n\n* The first file (21.txt) mentions that Michelle Vieth and H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n are divorced after a marriage of 1 year. This implies that they were once married, but now they are not.\n* Another file (7.txt) states that Michelle Vieth was married to H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n in 2001, but they divorced three years later due to the actor's infidelity.\n\nTherefore, based on these documents, I can conclude that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Michelle Vieth and H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n were divorced in 2004, and subsequently, Michelle Vieth got married to Leandro Ampudia. There is no information suggesting they are currently married."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state they are divorced.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Michelle Vieth and H\u00e9ctor Sober\u00f3n are divorced after a marriage of 1 year, and Michelle Vieth is currently married to Leandro Ampudia.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}